surfnlearn.com 2010-10-24

# Photoshop Tutorials 3DsMax Tricks and Tips - SnL Tutorial Search

We here at surfnlearn.com greatly respect your privacy and we hope that our users feel that the information they share with us is 100% secure and private. Here are the guidelines we follow at Surfnlearn to ensure your privacy and our integrity:

## Registration

In order to use this website to the full potential, we highly recommend you to first complete the registration form (Required for Forums). During registration a user is required to give their e-mail address, nickname, and other optional identifiers. This information is to identify the user, and for other users to interact with the user. None of this information will be sold, transmitted, or in any other way sent to any third parties. You also may be asked for your location, instant messenger names, etc but these are only optional and you may leave them empty.

## Cookies

Cookies are used to identify the user when he/she logs in, and for tracking purposes. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Once the user closes their browser, the cookie simply terminates. More specifically, we use this on surfnlearn.com in that the user would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site.

## Passwords

Surfnlearn staff will NEVER ask for your password. If someone does ask for your password or other info, please immediately notify us.

## Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that surfnlearn.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information.

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on the news so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an e-mail. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

## DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on http://www.surfnlearn.com/  
Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to http://www.surfnlearn.com/ and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL - http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .... Google Adsense

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on http://www.surfnlearn.com/ send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

http://www.surfnlearn.com/ has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. http://www.surfnlearn.com/'s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, please do not hesitate to [Contact Us](http://www.surfnlearn.com/contact_us/)! Thank you for your cooperation.
